Titled photographs
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Titled photographs
2.1.2.12.1
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1445
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - Kew Gardens, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Lyon rose, Kew Gardens, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Roses on wall, Kew Gardens, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Dorothy Perkins rose, Kew Gardens, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Dorothy Perkins rose, Kew Gardens, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - American Pillar rose, Kew Gardens, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Lady Gay rose, Kew Gardens, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Delphiniums, Kew Gardens, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - House boat on Thames River from Hampton Court, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Clematis, Hampton Court, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - The Blue Drawing Room, Buckingham Palace, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Prince Albert Monument, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  Box 1446
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - Trafalgar Square, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Alexander and Diogenes by Sir Edwin Landseer, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - St. John and Lamb by Bartolome Esteban Murrillo, in South Kensington Museum, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - London, England, circa 1900-1920; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - King’s College Chapel, Cambridge, England, circa 1900-1920; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Carlisle Cathedral, England, circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Chatsworth House, England, circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Cheddar Cliffs, Somerset, England, circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Tower in quadrangle, Founder’s Tower, Magdalene College, Oxford, England, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - View of the Cherwell, Oxford, England, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Hobby Drive, Clovelly, England, circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Durham Cathedral from southwest, England, circa 1900-1920; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Chapel of the Nine Stars, Durham Cathedral, England, circa 1900-1920; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Choir from the High Altar, Ely Cathedral, England, circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Choir Saracen, Exeter Cathedral, England, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Glastonbury Abbey, England, circa 1900-1920; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Nave, Gloucester Cathedral, England, circa 1900-1920; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Angel Choir, Lincoln Cathedral, England, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Lincoln Cathedral from river, England, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Liverpool, England, circa 1900-1920; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Elkhorn Lodge, Porlock, England, circa 1900-1920; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Porlock, England, circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Porlock, England, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Red Horse Hotel, Stratford-on-Avon, England, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Nave, Well’s Cathedral, England, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Nave, St. George’s Chapel, looking east, England, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Windsor Castle, England, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Sarcophagus, Royal Mausoleum, Frogmore, Windsor, England, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Five Sisters window, York Minster Cathedral, England, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - St. Ives, England, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Barrowdale, England, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Rural England, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Cottage, England, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Larches and beech trees, England, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - Pastoral England, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  - England, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1446)
  Box 1447
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - England, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - England[?], circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Cottage near Bettws-y-coed, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - The Leaning Tower, Caerphilly Castle, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Cottage near Caerleon, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Monkey on wall of Cardiff Castle, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - St. Mary, St. Cardiff, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Chapter House, Chester Cathedral, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Choir, Chester Cathedral, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Pictures in Chester, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Canal at Chester, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - House in Chester, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Conway Castle across bridge, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Conway Castle and bridge, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - River Dee near Eaton Hall, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - River Dee near Eaton Hall, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Flower house at Eaton Hall, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Gladstone, Hawarden, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Llandudno, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Road scene near Ruthin, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Old gateway, Tenby, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Boats at Tenby, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Tintern Abbey, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - St. David’s Cathedral, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Smallest house in Great Britain, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Sheep and trees near Tyn-y-Groes, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Sheep, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Old Welsh woman, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Fish woman, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Fish woman, Wales, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - The library, Abbotsford House, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Tomb of Sir Walter Scott at Dryburgh Abbey, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Soldier at Hollywood Castle, Edinburgh, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Edinburg, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - Station Hotel, Edinburgh, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  - On way to Edinburgh, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1447)
  Box 1448
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - Princess Street, Edinburgh, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Princess Street from Calton Hill, Edinburgh, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Princess Street Park, Edinburgh, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Royal clock, Edinburgh, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Edinburgh[?], Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Glasgow University, Gilmore Hill, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Glasgow, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Glencoe Mountains, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Glencoe, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Tombs of Kings, Iona Island, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Pass of Killiecrankie, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Silver Strand, Loch Katrine, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Road, near Loch Lomond, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Fish women at New Haven, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Washing day, Island of Skye, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Statue of Tom O’Shanter, Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Hayfield in Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Hayfield in Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Scotland, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - O’Donnell, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Monument in Dublin Park[?], Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Killarney Street, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Muckross Abbey, Killarney, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Ross Castle, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Colleen Bawn Rock, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Bridge between Bantry and Cork, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Linen Bleach Green, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Linen Bleach Green, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Isle of Avoca, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  - Isle of Tivoca, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1448)
  Box 1449
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - Road in Isle of Avoca, Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Ireland, circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Paris Avenue and L’Opera, France, circa 1900-1920; 3; 938S; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Tours Cathedral, France, circa 1900-1920; 4; 8442; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - In the Grand Gallery of Paintings, Louvre, Paris, France, circa 1900-1920; 5; 19912; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Galerie des Fetes, Chateau de Compiegne, France, circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Palace of Justice, Rome, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 7; 5177; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Pantheon, Rome, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 8; 25180; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Forum and Column of Trajan, Rome, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Coliseum seen through the Arch of Titus, Rome, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Statue of St. Peter, St. Peter’s Cathedral, Vatican City, circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Cour du Palais Ducal, Venise, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 12; 16 (19905); 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Vue d’Amalfi, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 13; 16093; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Berlin, Germany, circa 1900-1920; 14; 1723; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Munich, Germany, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Crevasses de Grindelvala, Swisse, circa 1900-1920; 16; 10710; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Exterior, Athens National Museum, Greece, circa 1900-1920; 17; 5278; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Sunken Gardens, Monaco, circa 1900-1920; 18; 18045; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Casino at Monte Carlo, Monaco, circa 1900-1920; 19; 21418; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Helsingborg, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 20; 380; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Museum, Helsingborg, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Lidkoping Bank, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Waterworks Tower, Lidkoping, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Redderholm’s Church, Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Strandvagen, Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Open café, Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Statue of Erickson, Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Main Street, Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Boulevard in Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Entrance to tunnel, Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Bergelsius statue, Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Museum, Stockholm[?], Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Birgeijailsgaten[?], Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Uppsala Castle, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Uppsala, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  - Botanical Gardens Museum, Uppsala, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 38; 3x4 color (Box 1449)
  Box 1450
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - Typical peasant, Sweden, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Pier, Rattork, Sweden[?], circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Church and houses, Rattork, Sweden[?], circa 1900-1920; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Bergen from rear of house, Norway, circa 1900-1920; 4; 103; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Bergen, Norway, circa 1900-1920; 5; 113; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Bergen, Norway, circa 1900-1920; 6; 169; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - University, Christiania, Norway, circa 1900-1920; 7; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Christiania, Norway, circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Fjosanger, Norway, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Panorama, Norway, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Major Arnold giving bread, Constantinople, Turkey, circa 1900-1920; 11; 114; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Panorama, Turkey, circa 1900-1920; 12; 5569; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - River-man sitting on wall, Kabul, Afghanistan, circa 1900-1920; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - The Terem Palace stairway, Russia, circa 1900-1920; 14; 2127; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - The Terem Palace stairway, Russia, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Corridor, Great Temple, Rameswaram, India, circa 1900-1920; 16; 12823; 3x4 b&w (Box 1450)
  - General view, looking east, Ajunta, India, circa 1900-1920; 17; 20215; 3x3 b&w (Box 1450)
  - General view, looking east, Ajunta, India, circa 1900-1920; 18; 20215; 3x3 b&w (Box 1450)
  - Interior cave, Ajunta, India, circa 1900-1920; 19; 20219; 3x3 b&w (Box 1450)
  - Interior cave, Ajunta, India, circa 1900-1920; 20; 20219; 3x3 b&w (Box 1450)
  - Lord of the Field, Bijapur, India, circa 1900-1920; 21; 20225; 3x3 b&w (Box 1450)
  - Cumbaconum, Hindu festival - 20,000 pilgrims waiting connection of Ganges with Sacred Pool, India, circa 1900-1920; 22; 21379; 3x4 b&w (Box 1450)
  - Gateway of Taj, India, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Taj Mahal, India, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Taj Mahal Hotel, India, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Prince in Indian uniform, India, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Old tower, palace, Tanjore, India, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - India, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - India, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - India, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - India, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Curious roots and trunk of the India-rubber tree, Peradeniya Garden near Kandy Ceylon, Sri Lanka, 32; color (Box 1450)
  - On board to Panama, circa 1900-1920; 33; 101; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - On board to Panama, circa 1900-1920; 34; 111; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Vessel passing through locks, Panama, circa 1900-1920; 35; 200x; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Map of Panama Canal, Panama, circa 1900-1920; 36; 224x; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Map of Panama Canal, Panama, circa 1900-1920; 37; 225x; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  - Panama Canal, Panama, circa 1900-1920; 38; 3x4 color (Box 1450)
  Box 1451
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - Road, Panama, circa 1900-1920; 1; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Bouganville, Panama, circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Panama, circa 1900-1920; 3; 227x; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Panama, circa 1900-1920; 4; 228x; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Panama, circa 1900-1920; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Panama, circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Panama, circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Avenue of Palms, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, circa 1900-1920; 8; 1130; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Corcovado from Botanical Garden, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, circa 1900-1920; 9; 7043; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Reception room in the Government Building, Santiago, Chile, circa 1900-1920; 10; 8753; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Silver Gates, St. John’s Church, Malta, circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 b&w (Box 1451)
  - Gold miners climbing to the summit of Chilkoot Pass, Alaska, circa 1900-1920; 12; 9208; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Bound for the Klondike Gold Fields, Chilkoot Pass, Alaska, circa 1900-1920; 13; 10191; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Agitized ruins of a great primeval forest, near Adamana, Arizona, circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Grand Canyon, circa 1900-1920; 15; 28200; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Grand Canyon from brink, circa 1900-1920; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Sunset from Rowaski across Grand Canyon, circa 1900-1920; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Sunset from Sunset Point, Grand Canyon, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - A tangled skein of mountain ranges from Moran’s Cove, Grand Canyon, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Geranium bed, Redlands, California, circa 1900-1920; 20; 7x118; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Marechal Neil rose, near Fresno, California, circa 1900-1920; 21; 10x219; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Calla lilies, Redlands, California, circa 1900-1920; 22; 18xx333; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Palm tree near Santa Clara, California, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Columbine, state flower of Colorado, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Seven Sister rose, Farmington, Connecticut, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Along the lake, Elizabeth Park, Hartford, Connecticut, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Rose arches, Elizabeth Park, Hartford, Connecticut, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Alpine Garden, Goodwin Estate, Hartford, Connecticut, circa 1900-1920; 28; 7x220; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - In the rose garden of Elizabeth Park, Hartford, Connecticut, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Poinsettias, Miami, Florida, circa 1900-1920; 30; 13555-9; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Cotton field, Atlanta, Georgia, circa 1900-1920; 31; 8xx166; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Cotton field near Atlanta, Georgia, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3xx173; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Rose garden, Thomasville, Georgia, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Old State House, Boston, Massachusetts, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - “Poet’s Narcissi”, Ames Place, North Easton, Massachusetts, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  - Lilacs, Sergeants’ Estate, Brookline, Massachusetts, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1451)
  Box 1452
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - North Platte Valley, Nebraska, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Spirea van Houten, Princeton, New Jersey, circa 1900-1920; 2; 19x182; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Watermelon field, near Swedesboro, New Jersey, circa 1900-1920; 3; 23417; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Statue of Liberty at night, New York, circa 1900-1920; 4; 213x; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - St. Patrick’s Cathedral, main altar and pulpit, New York, circa 1900-1920; 5; 7799; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - General Grant’s tomb, interior, sarcophagus, end view, New York, circa 1900-1920; 6; 16690; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Rose garden, Van Cortlandt Manor, Croton-on-Hudson, New York, circa 1900-1920; 7; 18570; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Metropolitan Opera House, New York, circa 1900-1920; 8; 70-18310; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Municipal Building, New York, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Woolworth Building, New York, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Luna Island and American Falls, winter, Niagara Falls, New York, circa 1900-1920; 11; 12420; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Rose garden near Great Neck, Long Island, New York, circa 1900-1920; 12; 18x560; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Long Island, New York, circa 1900-1920; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - John D. Rockefeller residence, Cleveland, Ohio, circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - “Caroline Teston”, rose hedge, Portland, Oregon, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Roses, magnolia, South Carolina, circa 1900-1920; 16; 18x788; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - South and west front view, Mount Vernon mansion, Virginia, circa 1900-1920; 17; 18506; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Canna bed in front of White House, Washington, D. C., circa 1900-1920; 18; 3xx892; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Patent Office, full view, Washington, D. C., circa 1900-1920; 19; 3944; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Hotel Bellview Stratford, Washington, D. C., circa 1900-1920; 20; 23133; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Shoshone Lake and Teton Mountains, Wyoming, circa 1900-1920; 21; 50; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Jackson Lake and Teton Mountains, Wyoming, circa 1900-1920; 22; 51; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Old Faithful Inn, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 23; 43; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Keppler Cascades, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 24; 48; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Lone Star Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 25; 49; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Feeding bear at canyon, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 26; 80; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Cleopatra Terrace, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 27; 93; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Buffalo near Fort Yellowstone, circa 1900-1920; 28; 97; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Office, Old Faithful Inn, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 29; 119; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Rotunda and balcony, Old Faithful Inn, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Hyman Terrace, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Mound Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Jupiter Terrace, Yellowstone National Park, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - In winter, 2 miles out on Behring Sea, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 b&w (Box 1452)
  - Basket of canning peaches, circa 1900-1920; 35; 16xx410; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Rose Ulrich Brunner, circa 1900-1920; 36; 18xx23; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  - Rose Ulrich Brunner, circa 1900-1920; 37; 18xx23; 3x4 color (Box 1452)
  Box 1453
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - Rose bush Ulrich Brunner, circa 1900-1920; 1; 18xx47; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Yellow roses on house, circa 1900-1920; 2; 18xx247; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - La France, circa 1900-1920; 3; 18xx278; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - La France, circa 1900-1920; 4; 18xx280; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Gruss an Teplitz, circa 1900-1920; 5; 18xx345; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Rambler, circa 1900-1920; 6; 18xx347; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Rose Gruss an Teplitz, circa 1900-1920; 7; 18xx393; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Lady Ashton rose, circa 1900-1920; 8; 18xx407; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Banks of roses multiflorus, circa 1900-1920; 9; 18x554; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Rose arches, circa 1900-1920; 10; 18x557; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Sunrise rose, circa 1900-1920; 11; 18x729; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Richmond, circa 1900-1920; 12; 18x731; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Captain Hayward, circa 1900-1920; 13; 18x857; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Caroline Testout, circa 1900-1920; 14; 18x864; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Narcissus, circa 1900-1920; 15; 4035; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - American Beauty rose, circa 1900-1920; 16; 18289; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Mrs. John Laing, circa 1900-1920; 17; 18900; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Niagara grapes, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Vetch, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1453)